[Earth, 2051]
[الأرض، 2051]
Wu Nongyu was shocked by the obsession
صُدم وو نونغيو من هذا الهوس.
[Cosmic Linguistics Research Association] Affinity B infected showed toward Affinity A carriers.
[رابطة أبحاث اللغويات الكونية] أظهر المصابون بالتقارب B ميلاً نحو حاملي التقارب A.
Wu Nongyu ran into a pillar,
اصطدم وو نونغيو بعمود،
and lost consciousness.
وفقد وعيه.
This is my interpretation of the alien script.
هذا تفسيري لنص الكائن الفضائي.
Does it sound reasonable to everyone?
هل يبدو هذا معقولاً للجميع؟
What happened next?
ماذا حدث بعد ذلك؟
Was Wu Nongyu taken away?
هل تم اقتياد وو نونغيو؟
And one more thing.
وشيء آخر.
Does Affinity A carriers attract Affinity B infected through scent?
هل يجذب حاملو العدوى من النوع "أ" المصابين بالنوع "ب" عن طريق الرائحة؟
Listen up.
استمعوا جيداً.
We are working on the information
نحن نعمل على المعلومات
of an alien civilization carried back by the exploring robots.
عن حضارة فضائية حملتها الروبوتات الاستكشافية إلى الوطن.
Let's keep this professional.
دعونا نحافظ على الطابع المهني لهذا الأمر.
Based on what we know so far,
بناءً على ما نعرفه حتى الآن،
Planet Y shares many fundamental similarities
يشترك كوكب Y في العديد من أوجه التشابه الأساسية
with Earth.
مع الأرض.
Does this mean the Affinity Virus
هل هذا يعني فيروس التقارب؟
could also emerge on Earth in the future?
هل يمكن أن تظهر على الأرض في المستقبل أيضاً؟
And the substance in that syringe,
والمادة الموجودة في تلك الحقنة،
is that the cure to the virus?
هل هذا هو علاج الفيروس؟
Let us continue the analysis.
لنواصل التحليل.
We will begin with what happened
سنبدأ بما حدث
after Wu Nongyu collapsed.
بعد انهيار وو نونغيو.
She had no idea how long she had been unconscious.
لم تكن لديها أدنى فكرة عن المدة التي قضتها فاقدة للوعي.
When she finally woke up.
عندما استيقظت أخيراً.
[Affinity] [Earth-Like Planet Y]
[التقارب] [كوكب شبيه بالأرض Y]
You hit your head last night.
لقد أصبت رأسك بضربة الليلة الماضية.
Mild concussion.
ارتجاج خفيف في المخ.
Do you remember what happened?
هل تتذكر ما حدث؟
It felt like a chaotic dream.
كان الأمر أشبه بحلم فوضوي.
I cannot remember it clearly.
لا أستطيع تذكر ذلك بوضوح.
Are you a doctor?
هل أنت طبيب؟
Turns out I come
اتضح أنني قادم
with horror movie sound effects.
مع مؤثرات صوتية لأفلام الرعب.
He looks just like
إنه يشبه تماماً
the person from five years ago.
الشخص نفسه قبل خمس سنوات.
Hello.
مرحبًا.
I'm Gu Yanqing, a researcher at the Genus Biological Research Lab.
أنا غو يانكينغ، باحثة في مختبر أبحاث علم الأحياء الجنساني.
You never came for the registration last night,
لم تحضر للتسجيل الليلة الماضية،
and we couldn't reach you by phone either.
ولم نتمكن من الوصول إليك عبر الهاتف أيضاً.
So I was sent to look for both of you.
لذلك أُرسلت للبحث عنكما.
In the end,
في النهاية،
I found both of you unconscious in the woods.
وجدتكما فاقدين للوعي في الغابة.
Call the police! Call them now!
اتصلوا بالشرطة! اتصلوا بهم الآن!
Attackers, lots of them, were in the woods last night.
كان المهاجمون، وكثير منهم، متواجدين في الغابة الليلة الماضية.
They killed a lot of people!
لقد قتلوا الكثير من الناس!
[Gu Yanqing, Researcher, Genus Biological Research Lab]
[غو يانكينغ، باحث، مختبر أبحاث علم الأحياء الجنسي]
Could he really be that person from five years ago?
هل يمكن أن يكون هو نفسه الشخص الذي ظهر قبل خمس سنوات؟
Are you feeling
هل تشعر
like you can't even
كأنك لا تستطيع حتى
move a muscle?
هل تحرك عضلة؟
It was the mushroom soup.
كان ذلك حساء الفطر.
It was toxic.
كان ساماً.
The soup you cooked last night contained a kind of hallucinogenic mushroom.
كان الحساء الذي طبخته الليلة الماضية يحتوي على نوع من الفطر المهلوس.
That's why you felt weak and had visions.
لهذا السبب شعرت بالضعف ورأيت رؤى.
No wonder I could trade a few moves with that attacker.
لا عجب أنني استطعت مجاراة ذلك المهاجم في بعض الحركات.
So it was all a hallucination.
إذن، كان الأمر كله مجرد هلوسة.
I told you not to eat those mushrooms.
قلت لك ألا تأكل تلك الفطريات.
Alright.
على ما يرام.
The toxins in your system should be mostly out by now.
يفترض أن تكون معظم السموم الموجودة في جسمك قد خرجت الآن.
Get ready.
استعد.
Come with me to see the director.
تعال معي لرؤية المخرج.
Hurry up.
أسرع.
The vibe is very different.
الجو مختلف تماماً.
But he looks far too much like that person.
لكنه يشبه ذلك الشخص كثيراً.
I still can't let my guard down.
ما زلت لا أستطيع أن أتخلى عن حذري.
[Genus Biological Research Lab]
[مختبر أبحاث علم الأحياء الجنسي]
Wow.
رائع.
This workplace is incredible.
مكان العمل هذا رائع.
This volunteer donated his body for our research.
تبرع هذا المتطوع بجسده لأبحاثنا.
From now on,
من الآن فصاعدًا،
he'll be your silent teacher.
سيكون معلمك الصامت.
Mr. Gu.
السيد غو.
Do you have time later?
هل لديك وقت لاحق؟
I'd like to ask you to review my paper.
أود أن أطلب منكم مراجعة بحثي.
Let's ask Mr. Ding to join us.
فلنطلب من السيد دينغ الانضمام إلينا.
You must be the new interns.
لا بد أنكم المتدربون الجدد.
[Xia Yuyan]
[شيا يويان]
Hello, Senior.
مرحباً أيها الطالب الكبير.
Alright.
على ما يرام.
I'll go bring the director over.
سأذهب لأحضر المخرج.
Make yourselves comfortable.
اجلسوا براحة.
I'll take care of them.
سأعتني بهم.
You two, just sit here.
اجلسوا هنا أنتما الاثنان.
Don't cause any trouble.
لا تسبب أي مشاكل.
Director.
مخرج.
I assume,
أفترض ذلك،
last night they ate some toxic mushrooms
تناولوا الليلة الماضية بعض الفطر السام
and passed out.
وأغمي عليه.
Toxic mushrooms?
الفطر السام؟
Mushrooms are great!
الفطر رائع!
It's been ages since I had any.
لقد مر وقت طويل منذ أن تناولت أي شيء.
I think about what to eat every day,
أفكر في ماذا سآكل كل يوم،
until my head hurts.
حتى يؤلمني رأسي.
Tonight, wild mushroom hot pot it is.
الليلة، سنتناول حساء الفطر البري الساخن.
Before dinner,
قبل العشاء،
let's take care of business first.
لنبدأ بإنجاز العمل أولاً.
[Gu Yanqing] Gu Yanqing's background looks solid.
[غو يانكينغ] تبدو خلفية غو يانكينغ متينة.
He is unlikely to be that person.
من غير المرجح أن يكون هو ذلك الشخص.
But the more I look, the more alike he seems.
لكن كلما نظرت إليه أكثر، كلما بدا لي أكثر شبهاً به.
Highly intelligent antisocial types
أنواع معادية للمجتمع تتمتع بذكاء عالٍ
are extremely good at disguises.
هم بارعون للغاية في التنكر.
What if Gu Yanqing
ماذا لو كان غو يانكينغ
is really just an alias for that person?
هل هو مجرد اسم مستعار لذلك الشخص؟
Should I warn the director?
هل يجب أن أحذر المخرج؟
Gu Yanqing
قو يانكينغ
has a criminal record.
لديه سجل جنائي.
He killed someone!
لقد قتل شخصاً!
Anyone who knows my secret
أي شخص يعرف سري
must die.
يجب أن يموت.
Head hurting again?
هل تشعر بألم في رأسك مرة أخرى؟
Let me introduce you.
دعني أقدمك.
This is the director of Genus,
هذا هو مدير شركة جينوس،
Mr. Ding.
السيد دينغ.
Hello, Mr. Ding.
مرحباً، سيد دينغ.
I'm intern Chen Yiyi.
أنا المتدربة تشين ييي.
She is intern Wu Nongyu.
هي المتدربة وو نونغيو.
We are Dongcheng University graduates, majoring in Biological Sciences.
نحن خريجو جامعة دونغتشنغ، تخصصنا في العلوم البيولوجية.
Second year.
السنة الثانية.
Very good.
جيد جدًا.
You look like well-behaved students.
تبدون كطلاب حسني السلوك.
(Watch on www.kissasia.co, .be, .org, .net, .id, .xyz )
(شاهد على www.kissasia.co، .be، .org، .net، .id، .xyz)
Mr. Ding.
السيد دينغ.
We got an emergency.
لدينا حالة طارئة.
Two bodies are missing from the morgue.
اختفت جثتان من المشرحة.
I meant to invite you to dinner,
كنت أنوي دعوتك إلى العشاء،
but a meeting came up.
لكن طرأ اجتماع.
Another time.
في وقت آخر.
Gu,
ل،
get them settled.
ساعدهم على الاستقرار.
Let's go.
دعنا نذهب.
This way.
من هنا.
The dorms are on the seventy-sixth floor.
تقع مساكن الطلاب في الطابق السادس والسبعين.
There is a cafeteria on the fourth floor.
يوجد مقهى في الطابق الرابع.
Help yourselves if needed.
ساعدوا أنفسكم إذا احتجتم لذلك.
Also,
أيضًا،
do not wander around at night.
لا تتجول ليلاً.
Understood, Mr. Gu.
مفهوم، سيد غو.
Chen Yiyi.
تشن ييي.
This is your room.
هذه غرفتك.
Good night.
طاب مساؤك.
Let's go.
دعنا نذهب.
In the Qiuxiao Manor Couple Murder Case,
في قضية مقتل الزوجين في قصر تشيوكسياو،
[Qiuxiao Manor Couple Murder Case] the police had listed the couple's son
[قضية قتل زوجين في قصر تشيوشياو] أدرجت الشرطة ابن الزوجين
as a suspect during the investigation.
كمشتبه به أثناء التحقيق.
However, no decisive evidence was found.
لكن لم يتم العثور على أي دليل قاطع.
The case remains unsolved.
لا تزال القضية دون حل.
Siyuan.
سيوان.
Do you remember the Qiuxiao Manor case from five years ago?
هل تتذكر قضية قصر تشيوكسياو التي وقعت قبل خمس سنوات؟
That suspect Xie you took away,
ذلك المشتبه به شي الذي أخذته بعيداً،
what happened to him?
ماذا حدث له؟
[Siyuan, overly talkative recently]
[سيوان، كثير الكلام مؤخراً]
Sorry.
آسف.
This is your room.
هذه غرفتك.
Mr. Gu.
السيد غو.
Good night.
طاب مساؤك.
I really cannot take it.
لا أستطيع تحمل ذلك حقاً.
Let me in.
دعني أدخل.
You...
أنت...
You don't...
لم تكن...
I brushed against the door and got fresh paint on me.
احتككت بالباب وتلطخت بالطلاء الطازج.
I really cannot take it.
لا أستطيع تحمل ذلك حقاً.
May I use your restroom?
هل لي أن أستخدم حمامكم؟
Even his silhouette looks so similar.
حتى شكله الخارجي يبدو مشابهاً جداً.
I need a plan.
أحتاج إلى خطة.
I have to check if he has that scar too,
يجب أن أتأكد مما إذا كان لديه تلك الندبة أيضاً.
without being noticed.
دون أن يلاحظ أحد.
Sorry.
آسف.
I was testing the water pressure,
كنت أختبر ضغط الماء،
and it splashed onto you.
وتناثر الماء عليك.
Let me wipe it off.
دعني أمسحه.
My pants are wet too. Should you help with that as well?
سروالي مبلل أيضاً. هل يمكنك مساعدتي في ذلك أيضاً؟
I will treat today like it never happened.
سأتعامل مع اليوم وكأنه لم يحدث أبداً.
I hope you focus on academic research from now on,
أتمنى أن تركز على البحث الأكاديمي من الآن فصاعدًا.
not on inappropriate matters.
ليس في الأمور غير اللائقة.
[Siyuan, overly talkative recently]
[سيوان، كثير الكلام مؤخراً]
Siyuan.
سيوان.
Why are you asking about Xie Xinxu?
لماذا تسأل عن شي شينشو؟
His name is Xie Xinxu?
اسمه شيه شينكسو؟
It's just that
الأمر فقط هو
these past few days,
خلال الأيام القليلة الماضية،
with my internship,
خلال فترة تدريبي،
I've been very anxious.
لقد كنت قلقاً للغاية.
I keep having nightmares,
ما زلت أرى كوابيس.
always dreaming of his unsettling eyes.
لطالما حلمت بعينيه المقلقتين.
You dream about him often?
هل تحلمين به كثيراً؟
- Why tell me only now? - Because
- لماذا تخبرني الآن فقط؟ - لأن
I was afraid you'd react like this,
كنت أخشى أن يكون رد فعلك هكذا،
so I did not dare tell you.
لذلك لم أجرؤ على إخبارك.
So what happened to him?
إذن ماذا حدث له؟
Siyuan.
سيوان.
He died four years ago, illness.
توفي قبل أربع سنوات بسبب المرض.
That puts me at ease.
هذا يريحني.
Siyuan, look.
انظر، انظر.
I'm settled in here,
لقد استقرت أموري هنا،
safe and sound.
سالمين معافين.
You do not need to worry.
لا داعي للقلق.
Don't stay up late. Good night.
لا تسهر لوقت متأخر. تصبح على خير.
The surveillance system failed.
فشل نظام المراقبة.
It did not capture how the two bodies disappeared.
لم يوضح التقرير كيف اختفت الجثتان.
This incident stays within these walls.
هذا الحادث يبقى داخل هذه الجدران.
Pull all surveillance from this building.
قم بسحب جميع أجهزة المراقبة من هذا المبنى.
Do not miss a single lead.
لا تفوّت أي فرصة.
Understood.
مفهوم.
[Morgue]
[المشرحة]
Why is there no signal in the cafeteria?
لماذا لا توجد إشارة في الكافيتريا؟
Mr. Gu must have misunderstood earlier.
لا بد أن السيد غو قد أساء فهم الأمر سابقاً.
He probably thought I was tempting him or something.
ربما ظن أنني أغريه أو شيء من هذا القبيل.
That was painfully awkward.
كان ذلك محرجاً للغاية.
She is mine.
إنها ملكي.
You have no right to touch her.
ليس لك الحق في لمسها.
♪You smell like something strange♪
رائحتك غريبة!
♪Like wood♪
♪مثل الخشب♪
♪Like wine♪
♪مثل النبيذ♪
♪Like the fading rain♪
♪مثل المطر المتلاشي♪
♪It's not a problem I can fix♪
♪ليست مشكلة أستطيع حلها♪
♪Maybe I'm just meant to be your toy♪
♪ربما أنا مجرد لعبة بالنسبة لك♪